[intriguing music playing]
[Ella] I think it really gives
the adventure Josh is looking for.
[Imogen] He'll love it.
Absolutely love it.
Yay! Great.
I really dig
the funeral parlor vibes here.
It was my grandparents' house.
Hey, do they haunt the place,
or is it just the curtains?
[Ella] Hey, Josh,
what kind of cake were you thinking?
Anything but cupcakes.
-Smart man.
-[Josh laughs]
Your mom likes me.
She also likes Phil Collins and pastels.
It's a low bar.
[phone buzzes]
Britney?
Uh… Crew thing.
What?
That's weird, I didn't get one.
There's another group text?
You're the other group text, Coxie.
Just figuring that out?
Oh, and the dinner
with Josh's grandfather.
At a restaurant run by an old friend
who just got her first Michelin star.
You guys are gonna love the food.
-It sounds amazing.
-[Ella chuckles]
You have a very beautiful home,
Miss Emerson.
Nice to see you again, Teagan.
-Bye.
-Bye-bye.
Bye.
-[Ella] Bye!
-[door closes]
What a well-mannered young man.
What?
["Ten Girls" by Circe playing]
Hey, plan for warm-up today?
Pick drills on the erg.
Everyone's posture is fine
for the first K, but then it falls apart.
I think we need to rework the basics.
And how's Ryder holding up in stroke?
Good. But he knows it.
[laughs]
So keep an eye on that.
You've managed to get a handle on
this team in a few weeks.
You just might whip them into shape.
One thing, though. Where are they?
All right, that's the last of the fries.
Uh, cheese.
Hey. Is anyone coming?
Coast is clear.
Ryder intercepted Mr. Wu,
and Baloo's side is good too.
But the question remains,
do we need to be doing this?
Yeah, Quaid,
what did this kid do to you anyway?
To me, nothing. But he's shaking down
the freshman on the novice team.
He's making him buy them loaded fries
at the commissary every day.
Beef.
So as payback,
we're giving him all the loaded fries.
Dude needs to be sent a message.
Everyone else is too scared to do it,
so it has to be us. Gravy.
Hang on, hang on. Incoming, incoming.
It's Principal Cabrera's grandkid.
Yeah, that makes sense.
-This is his car.
-Quaid!
-What?
What the hell are you doing to my car?
-Run!
-[Noah] Let's go!
[Cam] Come on!
["Gosports!!!" by couchgagzzz playing]
[boy] Quaid!
-Morning!
-Morning, morning, morning!
[guitar playing off-key]
[Quaid] Whoo!
You're flat!
Hey, sweet sack, bro!
Hey, she could do better!
Hello, boys.
Running late?
[song ends]
Detention? Instead of practice?
Did we forget the Head of the Laurence
Regatta is coming up?
Are we supposed
to hand it over to Westvale now?
Hope it was worth it.
Quaid! With me.
As for the rest of you,
you've been assigned essays.
Get to work.
[sullen music playing]
Stay.
Now you know where your rowers are.
Not the first student
to try and bully the principal's grandson.
I wasn't bullying him.
I believe the interior of Ethan's car
tells a different story.
[snickers]
Is that amusing to you, Mr. Quaid?
You've shown a pattern
of disruptive behavior
that has no place at Easton.
-Maybe you should look at Ethan.
-Ethan is the victim here.
You're out of chances.
I think…
we need to look at the big picture here.
All right? Quaid's a good kid.
He gives 100% on the team.
-Yes, he messed up.
-No, I didn't.
-I did.
-And he will never do it again.
As a matter of fact,
he's gonna keep his head down,
write his essay, and work really hard
so he can be in our boat
for our big regatta.
I'm sorry. I know I was wrong.
And I swear I won't do it again.
[Baloo] Hey, Perry.
What's your hack
for looking so good in photos?
Always be alpha.
No, I'm not into toxic masculinity.
No, me? Toxic masculine?
No, it's short form. ALPHA.
Angles, Lighting, Posture, Hair, Attitude.
Who's the pic for?
This guy I'm texting.
Boy's been generous with thirsty snaps,
and now he wants some back,
and I've got nothing.
Seriously? Even my grandma's got,
like, one emergency thirst trap.
Every time I try to take some,
I feel like an idiot. I'm more IRL sexy.
I'll hook you up with my ring light.
Once you get the vibes
and the lighting going,
can't go wrong.
First, obligatory family dinner party
for Granddad.
Right. "Thank you for the life of luxury."
-Then, it's time for the real party.
-[knocks on table]
Listen up, boys.
Y'all are invited to my young, rich,
and depraved birthday weekend.
Starting with Formula 1 go-karts racing.
-Sick.
-Then, MMA lessons and cage match.
Because Ryder needs some practice.
-Baller.
-And finally, the private jet to Atlanta.
Because we're all going to see Kendrick.
-[all exclaiming and whooping]
-[Perry] Get it on!
Yeah!
Going to Josh's party?
You're not even friends.
-It's a team thing.
-Mm-hmm.
And the team thing means
getting roped into Quaid's juvenile stunt
and getting detention?
Yeah, I know. It's immature,
but he's like a little brother.
I'd be a dick if I didn't.
If you say so.
-Have you never been on a team before?
-Uh, yeah. Swimming, tennis, track.
Those are solo sports.
What's your point?
Somebody never learned
to play well with others.
[laughing] Hey, I'm a better team player
than everyone else on the crew.
So we'll work on that.
-I'm back.
-[all cheering and exclaiming]
All right, all right, all right.
But he's on his last strike.
One slip and he's off the team.
Let this be a warning to all of you.
Behave yourself.
Oh, Quaid, hey.
I just wanna talk. Coxie to rower.
There can't be any more
of these childish pranks, okay?
Paybacks.
-Here, sorry, could you hold these?
-I know you think everything's a big joke.
But, hey, you are
a big part of our engine room.
We can't lose you, so pull it together.
No more of these pay…backs.
-Aye, aye, Captain.
-Why are you putting eggs in your bag?
Not my bag.
Huh?
[mischievous music playing]
-Quaid!
-[quietly] No, come on!
-Ugh!
-[whispers] Get over here!
We just got out of detention.
What the hell were you thinking?
I'm sorry. I know I was wrong,
and I swear I won't do it again.
[jet engine roaring]
Welcome to the Death Star.
I've always wondered
what Granddad's office looked like.
Impressive.
[Richard] I was nervous, too,
when I was first called into head office
on my birthday.
That's when my grandfather was CEO.
It's another Regis rite of passage.
Great Uncle Sterling is a VP,
and he's getting on.
His office could be yours one day.
Josh.
-You hear me?
-Yeah. I'm ready.
Just remember,
Granddad expects our family to lead.
This is your future, son.
Josh. Richard. Thanks for coming in.
I called you in today
because I'm looking to train a new VP,
starting now.
You can count on me.
Not everyone is cut out to be a leader.
Requires a certain skill set.
When I think about it,
everything I needed to learn as a leader,
I learned from rowing.
As the stroke seat. In stroke,
you have to follow your own rhythm,
ignore the pull of the crew,
and set the winning pace.
Josh has been in the eight seat
since he started at Easton.
[grandfather] Mm-hmm.
As a CEO, you must always do
what's best for the company.
Of course.
So how do you know
when you have the best candidate?
[tense music playing]
Uh…
When it beats the competition.
Come in.
Josh, starting this summer,
you'll be interning with Uncle Sterling.
And joining you will be Ryder,
the current stroke seat.
Glad to be on board.
Okay, birthday boy.
I flew in your favorite. Nobu.
Black cod miso, Wagyu dumplings, and…
Babe, are you okay?
Uh… No, I'm not.
It's just more of Regis drama.
Drama is what our families are all about.
What's up?
I think I just got demoted.
I'm supposed to train
to take over the family business,
but now my grandfather
wants it to be Ryder.
-Then get it back.
-How?
You know your grandfather. You tell me.
I have to get back in the stroke seat,
but that's gonna take time.
So you need something now.
-[ominous music playing]
-What other card do you have to play?
[exhales]
Wait. He's coming to my birthday party.
Yeah, I could, um…
I could invite the board
and get their support.
Show Granddad
that I'm a better leader than Ryder.
Not with "young, rich, and depraved,"
you won't.
No.
But I know what will.
[giggles demurely]
Why can't I do my homework
with the other guys?
Because you can't be trusted.
Now, just finish that problem.
[Teagan sighs]
Babysitting sucks.
That's why I let you raise yourself.
Help me choose a flavor
for Josh's birthday.
Which one tastes like privilege?
Coconut white chocolate.
[laughing]
Can't believe you're suddenly
an event planner.
[knocking on door]
What are you talking about?
I have thrown hundreds of parties.
Yeah, thrown, not planned.
Mom, when my old rowing club asked you
to bring food to the last regatta,
you doordashed it last at the minute.
Yeah. And those tortas were crazy good.
You're welcome.
Josh, Imogen.
Josh is here?
Quaid, come on.
-[makes shooting noises]
-No, focus.
I was just
putting some finishing details--
Oh, don't worry about that.
There is a new plan.
There is?
It is gonna be a tribute
to the history of Regis Airlines.
We need to invite the board,
our top shareholders,
Easton's rowing committee.
My mom's got a list.
Okay, so there… Uh, a new theme.
This looks like triple the guest list.
And it's still in six days?
Yeah. Why wouldn't it be?
Why don't you kids
just talk amongst yourselves
while Ella and I go over the plans?
We still go-karting?
-[Imogen] He wanted to tell you in person.
-No.
I know. It's a big ask,
but it's really important to my family
that this goes perfectly.
How does double your fee sound?
Prepare for takeoff.
In 1960, Regis Airlines had
bossa nova in their first-class lounge,
so all smooth period tunes, okay?
Wow. Mom, it's spectacular.
Did you just compliment me?
-[bossa nova playing]
-Don't push it.
[Ella exclaims]
[Imogen] Ella.
Let me welcome you
to Regis Airlines' golden age of flight.
The flight attendants
will be happy to serve
the finest hors d'oeuvres
from their carts.
And the signature cocktail
is a Paper Plane.
Ooh, I love the bossa nova.
Miss Emerson,
this is beyond what I imagined.
Sweet.
Thank you so much
for pulling this together.
A lovely party for a lovely young man.
I'm gonna check to see if the crew's here.
I've gotta go grab Britney.
Did you know that I'm a lovely young man?
So was Ted Bundy.
Hm. Did I really invite you?
Your mom did.
She needed someone charming at the party.
I would love for you to meet my husband,
Richard Regis. This is Ella.
Hi.
-Why do I know you?
-I used to watch you row.
I'm Matt Hayden's friend.
Right.
-You're the one that got away.
-Oh, I don't think he'd put it that way.
But I did move. And now I'm back.
Lucky him. Beautiful party.
I see some guests arriving.
Do you have enough servers?
I haven't seen any.
-Oh yeah, they'll be out shortly.
-Fantastic.
Send over some caviar bombs
as soon as they get here.
Yes, ma'am. [laughs]
Ugh. Um…
[phone line ringing]
-[woman] Hello?
-Hi, it's Ella calling. Where are you?
Is this too much bulge
or not enough bulge?
I don't wanna see your nudes.
-I see enough of that in the shower.
-It's not nudes. It's implied nudity.
Come on, Camouflage.
Okay.
Help a crewman out.
Don't send me into the wild
with a subpar thirst trap.
Yeah, the rest of us voted already.
I went with the muscle shot.
-Bro looks jacked.
-I like the one that looks like a Goya.
It's like no one's even been to a museum.
Please.
Muscles.
Thank you.
Okay, whoa, hold up, Q.
-You know the drill.
-It's a friend's party.
I'm not gonna do anything.
Look.
Okay, all clear. Come on.
Ooh… Who gets to do the pat-down?
[girl giggles]
Yeah, no, this is where I draw the line.
No coxie blocks.
I didn't think you were coming.
Well, I'm on Quaid duty.
It's been six days without an incident.
That might be the longest streak yet.
Look at you, figuring out the team thing.
This is significantly less
"young and depraved."
I don't know. Sometimes all you need
is a dry rosé and good conversation.
Yeah, if you're a Real Housewife.
-Well, what do you think?
-Ah!
It's genius.
Your grandfather's gonna be blown away.
I have a present for my future CEO.
-Oh my God. It's perfect.
-Yeah?
I love you, babe.
The pick-me energy in this room…
Josh knows
it's not just a one-person race anymore.
Did you see the look on my brother's face?
[both laughing]
Oh… Richard tried his hardest
to keep me in the mail room.
But I worked my way up.
And you will too.
If I take over for Uncle Sterling,
and you stay VP,
then we'll outnumber Richard two to one.
Keep it up, kid.
[urgent music playing]
911. Josh invited Cabrera.
-Oh, and she brought Fry Guy.
-If Quaid sees him, he's going to flip.
Nice to see you, boys.
-Teagan.
-Hi.
Where is Josh?
It was so thoughtful of him
to invite the school rowing committee.
Oh, he's over there.
Oh, thank you.
-Hey, that's mine.
-Mine now.
Cretin.
We need to find Quaid now.
-Come on.
-Okay, come on.
We need a plan, so let's just spread out.
Outside and exhibits and hallways.
Once we find him, we'll bring him here,
and, Crabby, you'll distract him,
and then Baloo and Cam,
you'll grab him and, uh…
throw him in here.
What? Why?
To trap him until Ethan leaves.
Great. Where do you want me?
Stop! Okay, guys.
We're not trapping Quaid,
our friend, in a closet.
-Give him a flashlight.
-Yes.
It's kidnapping, Crabby.
Also, have you seen him?
He's not fitting in there.
We're not doing it.
It's not fair to Quaid.
Hey.
Guys, we all know
that there's no stopping Quaid here.
-There's gotta be another way.
-If we don't do this plan,
then he'll get kicked off the team,
so come on.
-Why should we listen?
-Because I'm the coxie and I said so!
[scoffs]
Well, I don't think so.
I'm gonna go check the party.
I'm gonna go dance.
-We're gonna…
-…go this way.
[Cam sighs]
Oof.
Yeah, I know. I heard it.
-I can't take that back, can I?
-It's out there.
Come on. Maybe he went this way.
Hey, did you have to leave me hanging?
-I wasn't gonna manhandle Quaid.
-I was doing it for the team, you know.
You don't know what it actually means
to be on a crew.
Okay, well, explain it.
It's like a brotherhood.
We don't have to like each other.
We look out for one another.
But they don't look out for you.
[Cam] It's complicated.
If anyone picked a fight with me,
they'd have my back.
And I'd have theirs.
If you don't have their backs,
they're never going to listen.
Boy bonding is so strange.
I say we forget about them
and start our own team.
-Oh yeah?
-Mm-hmm.
And just be a pair?
It's a lot less drama.
Or just really concentrated drama.
Hey, I would be great in a pair.
I can compromise. I can get in sync.
But I get to lead.
There it is.
Where are the bartenders or the servers?
No one's cleaning up the messes.
Someone's raiding the bar.
Hey, what are you doing?
You got a corkscrew?
Hiya! I know you don't normally
serve the food,
but I'm in a bind and I--
Okay, nope.
That is a me problem, not a you problem.
Mom! There you are. Okay, don't freak out,
but there's no one working out there.
There's no food or booze.
Okay, you can't have people
rawdogging a party.
I know, just that
when we switched the party plans,
I forgot to tell the servers
about the new venue.
But they're coming though. They're coming.
They're close. I called them,
and they said they were an hour away,
and that was…
12 minutes ago. Oh God.
This is going to be a disaster.
I went to a Versace after-party once
where the booze wasn't delivered.
It took 15 minutes before the models
turned the champagne flutes into shivs.
Okay, well, we don't have 15 minutes.
The servers won't be here by then.
At least the wine's good.
Believe me, I would know. I helped
my favorite nanny train to be a sommelier.
Very impressive and illegal.
My parents are socialites.
I could get a PhD in parties.
Yours would have been killer
if you had enough servers.
-How would you like a job?
-A job?
Got a PhD in parties. You ever work one?
You can change in the bathroom.
-Are you nuts?
-I need all the reinforcements I can get.
And guess what?
No.
-I will hate you until I die.
-It's just till the servers get here.
Okay, Mom, I am trying to wrangle
a team of very resistant young men.
I can't do it in this outfit.
I know your team needs you, okay?
But I need you more.
Twenty-six hours of labor. Do this for me.
Before every race, I take two waffles,
smash a fried egg in the middle.
But the real trick is, you fold in
a bacon croissant for extra fiber.
Yum.
[intense music playing]
What?
She was there, like,
I dunno, but she's pretty cute.
If you'll excuse me,
I have important business to attend to.
We'll see, but…
[band playing bossa nova]
I must say, I am thrilled to be interning
with Regis Airlines this summer.
I'll be working
alongside my Uncle Sterling.
You two went to college together, right?
[Perry laughing]
-Love the retro look.
-Can I get a hot towel, miss?
And some pretzels. Not if they're salty.
-Is that a caviar?
-Guys, leave some for the real guests.
-Better listen to her. She's the coxie.
-Oh my God, she's the boss of us?
Hey, that's too many cookies.
[Perry, mouth full]
That's too many cookies.
That's a good cookie.
Hey, I was trying to help you guys.
-We didn't need your help. We found Quaid.
-What?
We stashed him there with that cute girl
so he wouldn't run into Ethan.
Really?
So where is he now?
I'll take that.
Philistine.
[guests grumbling]
Here, here, here.
We've been waiting 15 minutes.
Okay, well, I will save you
a trip back to the bar.
Kobe beef sliders, New Zealand
grass-fed lamb lollipops, wing tips.
One… one at a time. Some people
will claw your face for a tartare.
-Makes 'em malleable.
-[man] Lovely.
There's power here. I like this job thing.
Good luck with the shivs.
Need a copilot?
[playing soft bossa nova]
Hey, single malt neat. You know I got you.
Pour yourself one
when you're finished working bar.
Wait. Why are you working the bar?
Uh…
Oh.
Don't do… Don't do it.
Did you know
that this man makes a mean margarita?
I do love a margarita.
[laughs]
Yeah?
I've, uh, never seen
an event planner work the bar.
Oh. It's just until, uh…
Until now. [laughs]
Ah.
[quietly] Thank God.
Well, everyone's raving
about the canapés and the wine.
Well done.
I bet my wife hires you for Halloween
and our anniversary party too.
[laughing]
[Teagan] What are you doing?
Nothing.
Laxatives? Where'd you even get these?
-We're in a room full of old people.
-Quaid, you can't keep doing this.
I'm… I'm sorry.
Yeah, I was wrong, I…
[Teagan] Quaid.
Okay.
Why are you doing this?
Because you have to stop them
before it's too late.
Them?
First prep school I went to
was Laurelwood.
It was a nice school.
Then some dick like Ethan showed up.
It was a shove here, lunch money there.
No one did anything
because it was just one jerk.
Then someone else
tries to get away with something.
Before you know it, everyone's a bully.
I… I knew I should try to stop them,
but I was just a little kid.
But I'm not little anymore.
[pensive music playing]
I respect what you're doing, Quaid.
But you're gonna get expelled.
You can't afford to do this.
I know.
But I can.
Did you try the cake yet?
-I don't do gluten.
-Lame.
Maybe it didn't work.
Wait for it.
[Ethan groans quietly]
Are you okay?
There it is.
[stomach gurgling]
[girl] Oh…
[Ethan] Uh…
I'll be right back. Excuse me. Pardon me.
[Teagan squeals quietly]
So how do you know
when you have the best candidate?
When it beats the competition.
[men chuckling]
He's good. He's winning over the board.
All Granddad cares about is stroke.
And Josh ain't in it.
So all this doesn't matter.
[intimidating music playing]
This takes me back.
Dad.
Josh.
Incredible party.
[grunting]
[groans]
That was for the freshman!
[Ethan] Quaid, once my grandmother
finds out about this, it's over for you.
Quaid didn't do it.
Doesn't matter.
I'll have you both suspended.
Oof, Ethan. That's a pretty big threat
for someone who doesn't have toilet paper.
[cheeky music playing]
[Teagan clears throat]
If you wanna leave here with any dignity,
you're not gonna tell Cabrera,
and you're gonna leave the freshman alone.
Deal?
Deal.
[Teagan] Oh my gosh.
[Ethan groans]
[grunting]
-[Teagan] Ha!
-[Ethan] Dickbags!
I'm telling you,
she went beast mode, okay?
[guys laughing]
Remind me not to use the bathroom
for the next hour.
[all laughing]
-Well, if it isn't the Quaid Whisperer.
-You think it's about the friendship.
But it was really about the laxatives
we planted along the way.
[Teagan and Cam laughing]
[phone buzzing]
I've been added to the group chat.
Congratulations, Coxie.
[soft music playing]
Uh, what are you doing after the party?
Mm, I don't think anything.
I don't think the guys are doing anything,
so probably just head home.
Me too, I guess.
[Baloo laughs]
Wow, air ball.
What?
She wanted to ask you out.
Really?
What are you even waiting for?
I see how you look at her.
If you don't take the risk,
someone else will.
-Yeah, what about you?
-Hm?
You send that pic to that guy yet?
Ah…
-What are you waiting for?
-Ahh.
You changed?
You should have.
I'll be back in a minute.
[Perry] Mesh outfit?
Vulgar.
Banal.
Hey, guys. Has anyone seen my granddad?
Hell no.
-No, sorry.
-No.
Excuse me. Hey, wait a sec.
Uh, Granddad, where are you going?
Josh, happy birthday.
I thought you were enjoying the party.
It's a beautiful tribute.
I commend your ambition.
But you know what I see?
I see a lot of me and not a lot of you.
You're following someone else's rhythm.
Your gift's out front. Have a good time.
[dramatic music playing]
Babe. Babe. You gotta come. Come!
Oh, my God!
Wow, this… this is awesome.
-Thank you, Granddad.
-[car key bleeps]
All right!
Have you seen him?
No.
Please, everyone, enjoy the party.
Wow. Road trip ASAP.
Looks like it worked out
with your granddad.
[Josh] Yeah. The plan worked.
Thanks.
You're the best.
[gasps]
Is that medicinal or recreational?
It's my party. I'll get high if I want to.
The self-sabotage. Did you forget
we have regatta in two weeks?
You are such a buzzkill.
And you're a brat.
Don't you have to get back
to working my party?
Okay, you might have a big party
and the cool car,
but you don't have one ounce of class.
Well, if you like the car so much,
why don't you valet it?
Fine.
[upbeat music playing]
[engine revs]
[tires screeching]
She just stole my car.
[loon calling]
["Anywhere Else"
by Alice Costelloe playing]
♪ Please don't say it's all for me ♪
♪ I would rather be ♪
Dad just left, and now
his assistant's screening his calls.
Did something happen?
Clearly he hated the party.
He spent a total of five minutes here.
I need you to fire the party planner.
What? Ella? Don't be ridiculous.
You even said it was a perfect evening.
I want her gone.
♪ Anywhere, anywhere else ♪
♪ Anywhere but here ♪
Shit! [screams]
[tense music playing]
[urgent music playing]
How'd you know I was here?
Uh, rowing is your entire personality.
It wasn't a very hard guess.
It's not bleeding,
but it's a pretty bad bump.
Don't do that.
Do what?
I'm fine. I don't need you to--
Make sure you don't die?
Wow, you would seriously
rather drown than be saved by me.
Still deciding.
Mm-hmm.
And, yeah, this is… humiliating.
So, I'm gonna go back in.
I swear on Phil Collins' life,
I will let you drown.
Why are you making this a big deal?
You've only been awful to me
since day one.
Oh, you give as good as you get.
[soft music playing]
Yeah, I, uh… think it's time
you get back to your party.
[Josh] What, that train wreck?
It looked like everyone had a good time.
Except the one person it was for.
You?
Your grandfather.
Honestly, your family seems a little...
Insane? Yeah, I know.
People think that, um…
a family business
is a family that runs business.
It's really the other way around.
Well, maybe you'll get lucky,
and your entire life will blow up.
Worked for me.
I was joking.
I know.
Well, uh… better get back there.
Thanks.
For getting me out of the water.
You know, I know some guys
who were promised
a night of young, rich depravity.
I don't have a private jet,
but I do have the next best thing.
♪ I fought so hard just to love you ♪
-[cheers]
-[Cam] Yeah!
♪ I'm fighting harder ♪
♪ To let you go ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
Not bad, Tao.
Happy birthday, Regis.
-♪ You left a note on my door ♪
-♪ A note on my door ♪
Ella.
Oh, Imogen, hi. We're just getting
some more desserts going.
I've got something for you.
If you could come with me?
Okay.
Oh…
You can wait to pay me
until the end of the party.
It is the end of the party for you.
What? You're firing me?
The house manager
will take care of the rest of the evening.
Well, if I… if I did something wrong,
I can fix it.
I just think it's… it's best
if Richard doesn't see you here.
[ominous music playing]
It's not you. My family…
Richard's father sets everybody spinning.
But Richard is a good man.
I was married to a good man too.
I was in love.
I had a beautiful life, a fairy tale.
I didn't see the cracks, but you do.
Our husbands are not the same.
Don't lose yourself.
You can leave by the service entrance.
[Hayden] Hey.
Where are you going?
I got fired.
Why? Everyone's loving it.
Yeah, well, I guess it turns out
that if one person doesn't like it,
it doesn't matter.
Let me guess, Richard.
I know it wasn't perfect, but…
it was pretty great.
It's not about you. Richard's fired
already, like, six chauffeurs this year.
How are you still friends with him?
Ah… It's a team thing.
Look, I can't make any apologies for him,
but maybe I can make
your night a little bit better.
As you heard, I make a mean margarita.
[quiet, uplifting music playing]
Crab Shack has fresh limes, so I guess…
let's do it. [laughs]
Did you ask her out yet?
Did you send your pic?
[Baloo groans]
Baloo. You look hot.
Just send the pic.
[boy] Let's go!
Okay. Hold my hand.
[phone blips]
Feel better?
It's out there.
-[phone buzzes]
-Oh.
[exclaims]
Triple fire emoji.
You're in.
Your turn.
[exhales]
All right.
[phone buzzes]
Westvale? Our rivals.
Oh, crap.
[laughing]
It's a fun party.
Yeah.
I think the team's starting to like you
more than they like me.
Mm. That was always the danger.
I'm eminently likable.
Uh, Teagan,
can I talk to you about something?
-Sure.
-Teagan, your song's up.
[Teagan laughs]
Okay!
Uh.
♪ I'm comin' out of my cage
And I've been doing just fine ♪
♪ Gotta, gotta be down
Because I want it all ♪
♪ It started out with a kiss
How did it end up like this? ♪
♪ It was only a kiss, it was only a kiss ♪
♪ Now she's falling asleep
And she's calling a cab ♪
♪ While he's having a smoke
And she's taking a drag ♪
♪ Now they're goin' to bed
And my stomach is sick ♪
♪ And it's all in my head
But she's touching his chest now ♪
♪ He takes off her dress now
Let me go ♪
[Baloo] Hey, ho!
Have you seen Josh? Or the rowers?
♪ …saints into the sea
Swimming through sick lullabies ♪
♪ Choking on your alibis
But it's just the price I pay ♪
♪ Destiny is calling me ♪
-♪ Open up my eager eyes ♪
-[laughs mirthlessly]
'♪ Cause I'm Mr. Brightside ♪
-[song ends]
-[cheering and laughing]
-[Teagan] That was awesome!
-[all laughing]
[Teagan] Whoo!
[upbeat music playing]
[music ends]